UNITE Education Department Audio-Visual Materials 6000/022 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Education Department Audio-Visual Materials
1955-2001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
6000/022 AV
50.56 cubic feet
50.6 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
5751547
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 25, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 30, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections:
Textile workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Clothing workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees Education Department; UNITE HERE (Organization)
5751547
- 60 Minutes - CBS - 9/27/1992; Nightline - ABC - 9/29 & 9/20/1992; Paying to Lose Our Jobs, 1 (Box 1)
- Northeast Convention, 2 (Box 1)
- ILGWU Convention, 1986, 3 (Box 1)
  Scope and Contents
  MASTER
- ILGWU Convention Committee Reports (Tape 12), 4 (Box 1)
- ILGWU Convention 1986 Committee Reports T-5, 5 (Box 1)
- ILGWU Convention Committee Reports Tape 7, 6 (Box 1)
- ILGWU Convention 1986 Committee Reports T-6, 7 (Box 1)
- ILGWU Convention Opening Tape 1, 8 (Box 1)
- ILGWU Convention Committees Report Tape 3, 9 (Box 1)
- ILGWU Committee 1986 Opening Committees T-2, 10 (Box 1)
- ILGWU Convention 1986 Tape 9, 11 (Box 1)
- ILGWU Convention Committee Reports Tape 8, 1986; 12 (Box 1)
- ILGWU Convention Committee Reports Tape 4, 13 (Box 1)
- ILGWU Convention Committee Reports Tape 11, 14 (Box 1)
- ILGWU Convention 1986 Tape 10, 15 (Box 1)
- ILGWU convention 1989 Tape 8, 16 (Box 1)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 7, 17 (Box 1)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 8, 18 (Box 1)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 4, 19 (Box 1)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 3, 20 (Box 1)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 2, 21 (Box 1)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 1, 22 (Box 1)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 27, 1 (Box 2)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 26, 2 (Box 2)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 25, 3 (Box 2)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 24, 4 (Box 2)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 23, 5 (Box 2)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 22, 6 (Box 2)
- IU Convention 1989 Tape 21, 7 (Box 2)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 20, 8 (Box 2)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 19, 9 (Box 2)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 18, 10 (Box 2)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 17, 11 (Box 2)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 16, 12 (Box 2)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 15, 13 (Box 2)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 14, 14 (Box 2)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 9, 15 (Box 2)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 10, 16 (Box 2)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 35, 1 (Box 3)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 33, 2 (Box 3)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 34, 3 (Box 3)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 32, 4 (Box 3)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 31, 5 (Box 3)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 30, 6 (Box 3)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 29, 7 (Box 3)
- ILGWU Convention 1989 Tape 28, 8 (Box 3)
- FP&L Demonstration Master Tape 2, 9 (Box 3)
- FP&L Demonstration Master Tape 1, 10 (Box 3)
- FP&L Demonstration Master Tape 4, 11 (Box 3)
- FP&L Demonstration Master Tape 3, 12 (Box 3)
- Triangle Fire & Interview with Leon Stein, 13 (Box 3)
  tape #203
- ILGWU Tape 5, 14 (Box 3)
- ILGWU Tape 4, 15 (Box 3)
- ILGWU Tape 2, 16 (Box 3)
- ILGWU Tape 3, 17 (Box 3)
- ILGWU Tape 6, 18 (Box 3)
- Gus Tyler Interview #2, 1 (Box 4)
- Gus Tyler Introduction, 2 (Box 4)
- Gus Tyler and the Triangle Fire Memorial, 3 (Box 4)
- Gus Tyler - Triangle Fire Pictures, 4 (Box 4)
- Gus Tyler - Factory and Education, 5 (Box 4)
- Gus Tyler Clothing Factory, 6 (Box 4)
- Gus Tyler Chinatown Factory and Class, 7 (Box 4)
- Gus Tyler on Street, 8 (Box 4)
- Gus Tyler Meets With Japanese Education, 9 (Box 4)
- Gus Tyler on the Street, 10 (Box 4)
- Gus Tyler in Brooklyn, 11 (Box 4)
- ILGWU Tape 8, 12 (Box 4)
- ILGWU Tape 7, 13 (Box 4)
- Gus Tyler in Brooklyn, 14 (Box 4)
- Gus Tyler Meets with Japanese Education, 15 (Box 4)
- Gus Tyler in Brooklyn, 16 (Box 4)
- Labor Rally in Chinatown, 17 (Box 4)
- Chinatown Rally #1 -- Local 23-25 "We Are One", 18 (Box 4)
  source tape
- Drop in Center -- Brooklyn, 1992, Victor Sanchez, 1 (Box 5)
- Night of Culture #1, Victor Sanchez, 1992, 2 (Box 5)
- Night of Culture #2, Victory Sanchez, 1992, 3 (Box 5)
- ILGWU - 3/20/1990; tape 3 10/23/1992, 4 (Box 5)
- ILGWU, Tape 5; New Members Video, 5 (Box 5)
  Local 23-25 ILG -- MASTER
- Sheridan-Elson; ILGWU 3/20/1990, Tape 2, 6 (Box 5)
- Sheridan-Elson; ILGWU, 3/20/1990, Tape 1, 7 (Box 5)
- ILGWU, Tape 6; New Members Video, 8 (Box 5)
  Local 23-25, ILG
- Local 23-25, ILG - New Members Video, Tape 7, 9 (Box 5)
  Camera Original
- Local 23-25 "We Are One"; Chinatown Rally 2, Tape 2, 10 (Box 5)
  Source tape -- MASTER
- Local 23-25 - "We Are One"; Chinatown Rally 2, Tape 1, 11 (Box 5)
- Local 23-25 - "We Are One"; Chinatown Rally 1, Tape 3, 12 (Box 5)
- Local 23-25 - "We Are One"; Chinatown Rally #1 - Tape 2, 13 (Box 5)
  Source tape - MASTER
- Local 23-25 - "We Are One"; Chinatown Rally 2 - Tape 3, 14 (Box 5)
- Transfer of photos to tape - W.R. Smith Animation - 3/15/1990, ILGWU, 15 (Box 5)
- Transfer of photos to tape, W.R. Smith Animation - Reel #2, 4/19/1990 - ILGWU, 16 (Box 5)
- Domsey's #1 - 5/31/1990, 1 (Box 6)
- Domsey Rally #2, 2 (Box 6)
- Domsey Rally #3, 3 (Box 6)
- Domsey - Rosa Abrev Interview; Mock Election, 4 (Box 6)
- Domsey - Joe Blount; Father Estevez, 5 (Box 6)
- Domsey - Brice; Marie Judith Thelismond; Giles, 6 (Box 6)
- Edgar Romney Interview (Domsey), 7 (Box 6)
- ILGWU Solidarity Day #2, 8 (Box 6)
- ILGWU Solidarity Day #1, 9 (Box 6)
- ILGWU Solidarity Day, 10 (Box 6)
- ILGWU Solidarity Day, 11 (Box 6)
- ILGWU Solidarity Day, 12 (Box 6)
- Domsey - 3/17/1992 - Joe Blount, Father Estevez -- Tape 5, 13 (Box 6)
- ILG Mount Vernon 6/4/1987 #6, 14 (Box 6)
- ILG Mount Vernon Shop -- 6/4/1987 -- #2, 15 (Box 6)
- ILG Mount Vernon Shop #3 -- 6/4/1987, 16 (Box 6)
- Bronx -- Tape #11 -- LIG 6/5/1987, 17 (Box 6)
- LIG/OLIN -- Tape #8 -- 6/5/1987, 18 (Box 6)
- Tape #10 - LIG/OLIN 6/5/1987, 19 (Box 6)
- ILG Mount Vernon Shop #1 -- 6/4/1987, 20 (Box 6)
- LIG/Olin -- 6/5/1987 -- Tape #9, 21 (Box 6)
- ILG Mount Vernon #5, 22 (Box 6)
- ILG Mount Vernon #4 -- 6/4/1987, 23 (Box 6)
- ILG Mt. Vernon #7 -- 6/4, 24 (Box 6)
- ILG Chinatown - 6/10/1987, 1 (Box 7)
- ILG Chinatown #23 -- 6/10/1987, 2 (Box 7)
- ILG - Health Center -- tape #26, 3 (Box 7)
- ILG Chinatown -- #25, 4 (Box 7)
- ILG #27 - Health Center, 5 (Box 7)
- ILG #28 -- Health Center, 6 (Box 7)
- ILG #29 -- Health Center, 7 (Box 7)
- ILG -- 6/12/1987 -- Chinatown #20, 8 (Box 7)
- ILG Chinatown #22 -- 6/10/1987, 9 (Box 7)
- ILG Chinatown #21 -- 6/10/1987, 10 (Box 7)
- ILG Bronx #13 -- 6/9/1987, 11 (Box 7)
- ILGW Bronx #12 -- 6/9/1987, 12 (Box 7)
- ILG #15 Bronx, 13 (Box 7)
- ILG Bronx #14 -- 6/9/1987, 14 (Box 7)
- ILG Bronx #17 --- 6/9/1987, 15 (Box 7)
- ILG Bronx #16, 16 (Box 7)
- ILG Bronx #19, 17 (Box 7)
- ILG Bronx #18, 1 (Box 8)
- ILGWU, June 16, 1992, 2 (Box 8)
- ILGWU - June 16, 1992, 3 (Box 8)
- ILGWU - June 17, 1992, 4 (Box 8)
- ILGWU - June 18, 1992, 5 (Box 8)
- ILGWU - June 18, 1992, 6 (Box 8)
- ILGWU - June 18, 1992, 7 (Box 8)
- ILGWU - June 18, 1992, 8 (Box 8)
- ILGWU - June 16, 1992, 9 (Box 8)
- ILGWU - June 19, 1992, 10 (Box 8)
- ILGWU - June 15, 1992, 11 (Box 8)
- ILGWU - June 17, 1992, 12 (Box 8)
- ILGWU - June 17, 1992, 13 (Box 8)
- ILGWU -- June 16, 1992, 14 (Box 8)
- ILGWU - June 17, 1992, 15 (Box 8)
- ILGWU -- June 12, 1992, 16 (Box 8)
- ILGWU - June 15, 1992, 17 (Box 8)
- ILGWU -- June 15, 1992, 18 (Box 8)
- ILGWU -- June 12, 1992, 19 (Box 8)
- ILGWU Opposes NAFTA -- November 17, 1993, 20 (Box 8)
- ILGWU Rally -- November 10, 1993, 21 (Box 8)
- United Farm Workers of America -- No Grapes, 22 (Box 8)
  tape #573 // English version
- ILGWU/ACTWU Merge NY Network coverage -- February 20-21, 1995, 23 (Box 8)
- From Rags to Riches - HR22, 24 (Box 8)
- ILGWU Convention; Dues Debate -- LM47, 25 (Box 8)
- Hearings on Industrial Homework, Part 2, 26 (Box 8)
- Hearings on Industrial Homework, Part 1, 27 (Box 8)
- Sol Chaikin Address to Northeast Department - LM60 -- tape #74, 1 (Box 9)
- Today Show/Job Diplomacy - PO59 -- tape #71, 2 (Box 9)
- Talk With Those You Trust -- IM52 -- tape #60, 3 (Box 9)
- Evy Duty, 4 (Box 9)
- ILGWU Evelyn Dubrow Roast -- IL134 -- tape #56, 5 (Box 9)
- The Captive Audience Meeting -- OR67 -- tape #89, 6 (Box 9)
- Its Your Business': Working at Home -- HW64 -- tape #83, 7 (Box 9)
- 60 Minutes Report on Homework -- HW63 -- tape #81, 8 (Box 9)
- Fall River 50th Anniversary Celebration -- PO62 -- tape #79, 9 (Box 9)
- Eyewitness News Update On Import Rally -- TR68 -- tape #92, 10 (Box 9)
- A Time to Talk -- UH56 -- tape #64, 11 (Box 9)
- LVB #26 Black Trade Unions in South Africa -- IN45 -- tape #43, 12 (Box 9)
- LVB #22A/2 Segments -- tape #39, 13 (Box 9)
- ABC Nightly News/Homework -- HW61 -- tape #75, 14 (Box 9)
- America Works; Garment Worker Voncille -- UH51 -- tape #59, 15 (Box 9)
- Boycott - Another Way to Win -- CB50 -- tape #58, 16 (Box 9)
- From Rags to Riches (short version) -- IN49 -- tape #57, 17 (Box 9)
- The Wrath of Grapes -- OR13 -- tape #11, 18 (Box 9)
- In Search of ILGWU -- RE18 -- tape #16, 19 (Box 9)
- South Africa: Trade Unions -- SO14 -- tape #12, 20 (Box 9)
- Global Assembly Line, The (long version) -- IN12 -- tape #10, 21 (Box 9)
- You May Call Her Madam Secretary -- UH6 -- tape #5, 22 (Box 9)
- The Union Game: Beating the Union Busters, 23 (Box 9)
- Multi Shop/Join In -- UL46 -- tape #54, 24 (Box 9)
- The True Cost of NAFT / Labor Institute of Public Affairs, 25 (Box 9)
- Bessie Gabrilowich Cohn / Triangle Shirtwaist Co.; Group W Cable (part one), 26 (Box 9)
- ILGWU Convention '89 Fla./5 Segments -- tape #139, 1 (Box 10)
- Channel 11 News; ILGWU Protests -- TR70 -- tape #95, 2 (Box 10)
- ILGWU at Uretek -- HE69 -- tape #94, 3 (Box 10)
- 48 Hours on the Fashion Industry -- G174 -- tape #103, 4 (Box 10)
- Imports/2 News Segments -- tape #101, 5 (Box 10)
- Today Show, Part 2: Industrial Homework -- HW71 -- tape #97, 6 (Box 10)
- ILGWU Protests/2 News Segments -- tape #154, 7 (Box 10)
- Garment Manufacturing in Saipan -- UH120 -- tape #146, 8 (Box 10)
- Channel 2 News on Sweatshops in NYC -- SW75 -- tape #105, 9 (Box 10)
- The Organizer -- UN119 -- tape #145, 10 (Box 10)
- Union Label Spoofs -- UL78 -- tape #112, 11 (Box 10)
- Press Conference With Pauline Pepe -- UH109 -- tape #138, 12 (Box 10)
- ILGWU Endorses Dinkins/3 Segments -- tape #137, 13 (Box 10)
- China Protests in NYC/6 Segments -- tape 136, 14 (Box 10)
- NBC-TV Business View on ILGWU -- IN79 -- tape #113, 15 (Box 10)
- The American Worker's Story -- UH96 -- tape #135, 16 (Box 10)
- News at Five on Labor Memorial Ceremony -- HE81 -- tape #115, 17 (Box 10)
- ILGWU Union Label Commercials -- UL80 -- tape #114, 18 (Box 10)
- Triangle Commemorative -- UH77 -- tape #110, 19 (Box 10)
- Hispanic Horizons - Sweatshops -- SW133 -- tape #155, 20 (Box 10)
- ILGWU in Florida/Compiled/4 Segments -- tape #150, 21 (Box 10)
- Al Gore, ILGWU Convention 1989 -- tape #152, 22 (Box 10)
- Gus Tyler on Good Morning America -- HW/SW118 -- tape #143, 23 (Box 10)
- USA Tonight-ILGWU Dispute -- ST117 tape #142, 24 (Box 10)
- David Dinkins Noticias -- PO115 -- tape #141, 25 (Box 10)
- Kitty Dukakis Tours Garment Factory -- tape #153, 26 (Box 10)
- MacNeil/Lehrer on Homework -- HW76 -- tape #109, 27 (Box 10)
- ILGWU Evelyn Dubrow Roast -- IL134 -- ILGWU/Politics -- tape #156, 28 (Box 10)
- 1989 ILGWU Convention -- tape #36 -- IL169, 29 (Box 10)
- Dr. Ruth Presentation tape 1 -- RE181 -- tape #210, 1 (Box 11)
- ILGWU FP&L Demonstration MASTER EDIT -- SO176 - tape #205, 2 (Box 11)
- Dr. Ruth Presentation tape 3 -- RE183 -- tape #212, 3 (Box 11)
- Dr. Ruth Presentation -- tape 2 -- RE182 -- tape #211, 4 (Box 11)
- Triangle Fire and Interview with Leon Stein -- UH175 -- tape #203, 5 (Box 11)
- Narration for the Triangle Fire -- UH174 -- tape #202, 6 (Box 11)
- 1989 ILGWU Convention -- Tape 39 -- IL172 -- tape #200, 7 (Box 11)
- 1989 ILGWU Convention -- Tape 38 -- IL171 -- Tape #199, 8 (Box 11)
- Sol Chaikin Archive - Tape 2 -- UH189 -- Tape #221, 9 (Box 11)
- Sol Chaikin Archine - Tape 4 -- UH191 -- Tape #223, 10 (Box 11)
- Sol Chaikin Archive - Tape 3 -- UH190 -- tape #222, 11 (Box 11)
- News Report on Garment Workers Walkout -- TR185 -- Tape #214, 12 (Box 11)
- Dr. Ruth Presentation Tape 4 -- RE184 -- Tape #213, 13 (Box 11)
- Sol Chaikin Archine Tape 1 -- UH188 -- Tape #220, 14 (Box 11)
- Evy Dubrow -- PO187 -- Tape #219, 15 (Box 11)
- Evy Dubrow -- PO187 -- Tape #219, 16 (Box 11)
- ILGWU: Labor Day Montage -- LM213 -- tape #246, 1 (Box 12)
- Triangle Fire, The (6 minute version)-- UH238, 2 (Box 12)
- Hederick Sweatshop Package part 2 -- SW216 -- tape #249, 3 (Box 12)
- ILGWU Convention Tape 11 -- IL214 -- tape #247, 4 (Box 12)
- From the Bedside to the Table -- OR212 -- Tape #243, 5 (Box 12)
- Channel 9 News - Industrial Homework -- HW211 -- tape #240, 6 (Box 12)
- Sol Chaikin Archive Tape 5 -- UH192 -- tape #224, 7 (Box 12)
- Compilation Tape/5 Segments -- tape #226, 8 (Box 12)
- American Family Day Celebration -- tapes 4-6 -- LM198 -- tape #229, 9 (Box 12)
- American Family Day Celebration Tapes 1-3 -- LM197 -- tape #228, 10 (Box 12)
- ILGWU on the Move - IL239 -- tape #282, 11 (Box 12)
- Import Flood; Job Drain -- TR222 -- tape #261, 12 (Box 12)
- We Are One -- CB221 -- tape #260, 13 (Box 12)
- Industrial Homework -- HW220 -- tape #259, 14 (Box 12)
- Straight Talk - Sweatshops Seg. 1 -- SW219 -- tape #257, 15 (Box 12)
- Garment Industry and Foreign Imports -- TR21 - tape #256, 16 (Box 12)
- NBC News - The New Sweatshops -- SW217 -- tape #51, 17 (Box 12)
- The ILGWU on the Move -- IL253 -- Tape #295, 1 (Box 13)
  MASTER-Looped
- Channel 2 News - Sweatshop Report - SW251 -- tape #293, 2 (Box 13)
- Sol Chaikin -- UH250 -- tape #289, 3 (Box 13)
- ILGWU Photographs -- IL249 -- tape #288, 4 (Box 13)
- Channel 4 News -- Kamali -- OR243 -- tape #286, 5 (Box 13)
- Channel News -- Homework -- HW242 -- tape #285, 6 (Box 13)
- The Nightly Business Report - ILGWU Story -- EC241 -- tape #284, 7 (Box 13)
- Triangle Fire Photographs #2 -- UH257 -- tape #298, 8 (Box 13)
- Triangle Fire Photographs #1 -- UH256 -- tape #297, 9 (Box 13)
- The Sweatshop and Homework Menace -- HW/SW265 -- tape #301, 10 (Box 13)
- Triangle Fire Presentation 1986 -- UH258 -- tape #299, 11 (Box 13)
- Channel Eye On -- IM254 -- tape #296, 12 (Box 13)
- L.A. News Report on Homework Hearings -- HW261 -- tape #300, 13 (Box 13)
- Organizing on the Move -- OR268 -- tape #304, 14 (Box 13)
- We Are One -- tape #260, 15 (Box 13)
  Kheel Center Dupl.
- ILGWU - Debate on English as Second Language -- IM299 - tape #352, 1 (Box 14)
- Channel 5 News - Dinkins -- LM289 -- tape #337, 2 (Box 14)
- Triangle Fire 75th Anniversary -- tape #328, 3 (Box 14)
- Homework in Dallas -- HW291 -- tape #340, 4 (Box 14)
- 1989 ILGWU Convention VHS Unedited -- IL277 -- tape #323, 5 (Box 14)
- Sweatshops Unedited -- SW276 -- tape #322, 6 (Box 14)
- Trouble on Fashion Avenue -- IL271 -- tape #317, 7 (Box 14)
- Homeworkers - New Jersey -- HW270 -- tape #314, 8 (Box 14)
- Sweatshops - Triangle Fire -- UH207 -- tape #356, 9 (Box 14)
- Today Show - Sweatshops -- SW279 -- tape #327, 10 (Box 14)
- Sweatshops/4 Segments - tape #321, 11 (Box 14)
- Voices -- WO269 -- tape #305, 12 (Box 14)
- ILGWU Labor Day Parade 1983 -- LM311 -- tape #360, 13 (Box 14)
- Creating Jobs: Whose Problem is it? -- EC310 -- tape #359, 14 (Box 14)
- The Chaikin Decade -- TR 312 -- tape #361, 15 (Box 14)
- Evelyn Dubrow Roast 1 -- UH300 -- tape #353, 16 (Box 14)
- Evelyn Dubrow Roast 2 -- UH301 -- tape #354, 17 (Box 14)
- ILGWU - Report to Convention 1980 -- 4/23/1984, 18 (Box 14)
- NBC Today - Vermont Knitters, 19 (Box 14)
- Noticias 41: 3/20/1991: Triangle Fire -- UH331 -- tape #388, 1 (Box 15)
- Domsey Strike, The #5 -- ST317 -- tape #368, 2 (Box 15)
- Kids at Work - Danger -- HW/SW337 -- tape #390, 3 (Box 15)
- Domsey Strike Footage, The #2 -- ST314 -- tape #365, 4 (Box 15)
- If You Don't Come in Sunday - Don't Come In Monday -- UH327 -- tape #379, 5 (Box 15)
- The Today Show - Lifting Homework Bans -- HW318 -- tape #369, 6 (Box 15)
- Channel 7 News: 3/26/1990: Triangle Fire -- UH347 -- tape #408, 7 (Box 15)
- Tiananmen Square-LU Jing Hua, 8 (Box 15)
- Your More, Your Pain and Silent Danger -- tape #315, 9 (Box 15)
- ILGWU Chorus at Convention -- IL330 -- tape #384, 10 (Box 15)
- Domsey Strike Footage, The #1 -- ST313 -- tape #364, 11 (Box 15)
- ILGWU 'On Stage' -- UL342 -- tape #395, 12 (Box 15)
- ILGWU Advertising Report to Convention 1989 -- UH326 -- tape #377, 13 (Box 15)
- Joining Hands -- IL345 -- tape #400, 14 (Box 15)
- Justice for Janitors -- OR336 -- tape #389, 15 (Box 15)
- Joining Hands -- IL345 -- tape #400, 16 (Box 15)
- Cuomo Speaks with the ILGWU in Miami -- PO325 -- tape #376, 17 (Box 15)
- Joining Hands -- IL345 -- tape #400, 18 (Box 15)
- Dan Rather - Sweatshops -- SW328 -- tape #381, 19 (Box 15)
- Offen Brother's - Holocaust Stories -- IN329 -- tape #383, 20 (Box 15)
- CBS News: 9/7/1990: Ellis Island, 21 (Box 15)
- ILGWU Endorses David Dinkins -- PO322 -- tape #274, 22 (Box 15)
- 1990 Labor Day Parade -- IL346 -- tape #402, 23 (Box 15)
- Channel 4 News: 3/26/1990: Triangle Fire #1 -- UH349 -- tape #408, 24 (Box 15)
- Struggle at Domsey -- OR338 -- tape #391, 25 (Box 15)
- Solidarity Day '91 / Labor Institute of Public Affairs, 1991; 1 (Box 16)
- Wall to Wall, 2 (Box 16)
- El Paso Footage -- May 2, 1991, 3 (Box 16)
- Sonia's Huelga - Tape #1 - May 1, 1991, 4 (Box 16)
- Labor Day in Chinatown, 5 (Box 16)
- Labor Dispute at Domsey trading -- 3/18/1991, 6 (Box 16)
- Salvation Army/Goodwill controversy -- 2/11/1991, 7 (Box 16)
- Full Show -- CrossFire -- 6/11/1991, 8 (Box 16)
- News Stories on Oct. 8th, Rally for Health Care, 9 (Box 16)
- 1991 AFL-CIO Convention Video Roll-Ins, 10 (Box 16)
- DCB Strike 5/2, 11 (Box 16)
- The Real Story - NYC Sweatshops -- 11/6/1991, 12 (Box 16)
- Sweat Shops/The Garment Industry -- April 15, 1991, 13 (Box 16)
- VDT Legislation in Suffolk County - May 23rd, 14 (Box 16)
- Songs of Solidarity: Solidarity Day '91, 1991; 15 (Box 16)
- Domsey an Grev!, 16 (Box 16)
- Anniversary of the Triangle Shirt Waist Fire -- March 26, 1990, 17 (Box 16)
- JOU JOU Design Workers - Back Wages -- September 13, 1990, 18 (Box 16)
- Boris Yeltsin, 19 (Box 16)
- A & S Plaza/Total Energy Label Boycott -- May 23, 1991, 20 (Box 16)
- ILGWU -- Sheridan-Elson ILGWU -- 12/3/1992, 21 (Box 16)
- El Salvadoran Immigrants / Dave Marsh Reporting, 22 (Box 16)
- ILGWU / Restored Murals -- Dec. 10, 1991, 23 (Box 16)
- Garment Center Rally Coverage - Ch. 2 -- 11/1/1984, 1 (Box 17)
- Friday, June 6th, 2 (Box 17)
- Jay Mazur / McNeill-Lehrer Homework Ban - Sept. 1986, 3 (Box 17)
- Segment on El Paso sweat shops - 3/14/1991, 4 (Box 17)
- New Immigrants, In NYC; Raw Footage - Oct. 1990, 5 (Box 17)
- EP Rainfair, 6 (Box 17)
- Max Zimm Channel 9 News -- 6/23/1984; Union Label Ads, 7 (Box 17)
- Rally Coverage -- 11/1/1984, 8 (Box 17)
- Solidarity Day 8/30/1991 -- ILGWU Chorus/Willie Nelson, 9 (Box 17)
- Local 23-25, ILGWU CCTN; Television spot for Cantonese English classes - Sept. 9, 1985, 10 (Box 17)
- Advertising for Community Service Dept.; Local 23-25, ILGWU -- April 1988, 11 (Box 17)
- Would You Let Someone Do This to Your Sister?, 12 (Box 17)
- AFL-CIO Detroit - 11/11/1991 -- tape #1, 13 (Box 17)
- It didn't have to happen: Preventing cumulative trauma disorders, 1990; 14 (Box 17)
- Chinatown Adult Education Week - ILGWU worker family education Nov. 20, 1987, 15 (Box 17)
- Mazur Interview - Victor Sanchez 1992, 16 (Box 17)
  dub
- ILGWU/Triangle Shirt Waist Fire Anniversary; March 25, 1992, 17 (Box 17)
- AFL-CIO Community Services / The Union Counselor, 1991; 18 (Box 17)
- Changing Attitudes: Union Members Talk About AIDS, 19 (Box 17)
- Triangle Rally / Victor Sanchez -- 1991, 20 (Box 17)
- Report to Convention 1986, 21 (Box 17)
- ILGWU Endorses Nydia Velasquez -- Tape #586, 22 (Box 17)
- Daily News Strike -- tape #584, 23 (Box 17)
- Susan Cowell, ILGWU/Affordable Healthcare -- June 5, 1991, 24 (Box 17)
- Campaign to End Childhood Hunger, 25 (Box 17)
- ILGWU Protest, 26 (Box 17)
- ILGWU-HTPT Rally Edited 1992 -- tape #486, 27 (Box 17)
- Sinovision - Child Care -- 11/15/1991, 1 (Box 18)
- Domsey Rally w/Jesse Jackson -- Picket Line -- 7/23/1990, 2 (Box 18)
- Ghetto, 3 (Box 18)
  Title is very hard to read
- Domsey Rally w/Jesse Jackson -- Rally Speakers -- 7/23/1990 [reels 3 &4], 4 (Box 18)
- ILGWU Convention Imports -- tape #582, 5 (Box 18)
- Report to Convention 1989 -- tape #589, 6 (Box 18)
- Jay on NAFTA -- tape #590, 7 (Box 18)
- Buy American Segment -- tape #592, 8 (Box 18)
- Report to Convention 1992, 9 (Box 18)
- Nightline: Apparel Job -- tape #575, 10 (Box 18)
- ILGWU Chorus at Grand Central Station -- tape #587, 11 (Box 18)
- On Stage II -- tape #581, 12 (Box 18)
- Moneyline: Segment with Jay Mazur -- tape #591, 13 (Box 18)
- Union Label Committee Presentation -- tape #585, 14 (Box 18)
- ILGWU: UNITE and Fight, 15 (Box 18)
- ILGWU: UNITE and Fight -- tape #579, 16 (Box 18)
- Nightline: Maidenform -- tape #574, 17 (Box 18)
- Domsey Rally w/Jesse Jackson - Rally Tail End -- 7/23/1990, 18 (Box 18)
- Steward Education -- 2/28/1990, 19 (Box 18)
- Jay Mazur, 20 (Box 18)
- Triangle Fire, 21 (Box 18)
- ILGWU - conference -- 7/28/1990, 22 (Box 18)
- Domsey Workers: You are the Union, 1992; 23 (Box 18)
- Talleres de Sudor -- Ana Azey, 24 (Box 18)
- Local 23-25 Television Spots: 1.Member Assistance Program; 2.Statue of Liberty Appeal -- 3/7/1996, 25 (Box 18)
- ILGWU - June 19, 1992, 26 (Box 18)
- Hilary Clinton/ILGWU Miami Coverage, 27 (Box 18)
- Kerr Mill/Fall River Fire Footage, 28 (Box 18)
- Foreign Agent -- tape #597, 1 (Box 19)
- Apparel Jobs Abroad -- tape #596, 2 (Box 19)
- Labor Day Rally -- tape #595, 3 (Box 19)
- Segment on DC Labor Rally -- tape #594, 4 (Box 19)
- ILGWU Tokyo Present Union Label -- tape #629, 5 (Box 19)
- The Golden Door / presented by the New York Jt. Bd./ACTWU, 6 (Box 19)
- 1989 Labor Day Parade -- tape #628, 7 (Box 19)
- Boston ILGWU/Industry -- tape #627, 8 (Box 19)
- Strike & Boycott of La Mode Du Golf Producs, 9 (Box 19)
- NY92 Fashion Show and SONY Times Square Feature, 10 (Box 19)
- ACTWU PAC - Dub -- 2/24/1989, 11 (Box 19)
- Segment on Healthcare Proposals -- tape #633, 12 (Box 19)
- Leaving Home, 13 (Box 19)
- Labor at the Crossroads Presents: No More Bandaids: Curing the Health Care Crisis, 14 (Box 19)
- IAM Members Decide - September 1992, 15 (Box 19)
- Triangle Shirtwaist Factory Fire, 16 (Box 19)
- Rain Fair -- tape #635, 17 (Box 19)
- Segment on sweat shops - Nightly News - 3/1/1992, 18 (Box 19)
- Segment on Sweat Shops - tape #636, 19 (Box 19)
- Made in China -- 60 Minutes -- 9/15/1991, 20 (Box 19)
- Triangle Fire Anniversary Remembrance -- March 25, 1988, 21 (Box 19)
- French Daycare Tour -- March 21, 22 (Box 19)
- Fiber Fabric & Apparel Coalition for Trade - Statistics -- 2/29/1988, 23 (Box 19)
- Report on Minimum Wage -- tape #598, 24 (Box 19)
- ILGWU/TB Study - Local New York, Network Coverage -- October 19-20, 1992, 25 (Box 19)
- ILGWU/Triangle Shirt Waist Fire Anniversary, March 25, 1992, 26 (Box 19)
- Skills Crisis, 27 (Box 19)
- Empowering Workers -- tape #624, 28 (Box 19)
- Workplace Diversity -- tape #625, 29 (Box 19)
- Work vs. the Family -- tape #626, 30 (Box 19)
- Garment Workers/TB - Noticiero 47 -- October 19, 1992, 31 (Box 19)
- ILGWU/Fire Drill Rally in Garment District, 1991; 32 (Box 19)